From the shadows of the subconscious, to the chaos of the cosmic scrolls, this is Psyche Awakens.
Crowd, whoosh, sparkly chimes, thundercrack.
You smooth mystical.
Yo, welcome to the madness, buckle in tight, tear it on deck, third eye in flight.
Truth's get told, it goes unfold, we stir the soul with a tea surf cold.
Trolls be dropping, spirits in the chat and the vibes ain't stopping
Lenore's on guard, tricks bringin' love
Lola, Rudy Marble's fan from above
It's like the Awake has stepped in the flame
We call your truth, we say your name
It's wild, it's real, it's so deep play
Now grab your tea and slay the dead
It's like the Awake has don't look away
Your shadow's talkin', it came to stay
We laugh, we cry, we speak
We scream, live from the madness
This ain't no dream
hello guys let's clear the air a little bit
now i don't know how big of a fan few times is on my show he's
i mean i'm just being accused of all these things on other channels that are not true like i have never
put my um i've actually done one members only live which you're allowed to do members only lives
but i've never like said
Maybe I think maybe I won occasion a few months ago
I may have you know tried out something or it's like I said, okay
Well today only members and mods or donators on which on the panel
But it wasn't a regular thing and it's like you acting like that's the rule and
Listen word misunderstanding
No, but uh
I don't know how long I'll be. You know I've been very tired lately not feeling so perfect, but I thought I'd come for a couple hours
Oh, I did try to go to betas and like you know be friendly and stuff
everyone's just like
Was like, you know the chair chat is kind of on my side a little bit, but
She's I don't know why she's doing so mean
But maybe we'll work it out, you know, I don't like to yeah
I know good times is like just he doesn't even come here. Like how does he even know like a
Even if I did have that system, that's my system to have it's like I don't go over people's channels
Tell them how to run their channel or anything like that. It's just so so funny how it's like I'm
Everyone's just like allowed to say I'm
Big so horrible and stuff and
Right
But I'm not playing a victim or anything like that, you know, I'm a big boy, you know, I can like handle
handle it
She stood up they just noticed the guys I didn't go where they're starting trouble. I started their new family and stuff
Hey, time. How are you? I?
Trying to be friendly and I get attacked and I just don't feel like sitting there just being
Called like the basic garbage in the world, right? Thank you, Samantha
I come here, I just try to have a good time.
I try to maybe make a little extra
so I can continue to do this full time.
I did already, you know,
I'm keeping the panel open tonight
because I had a nice donation earlier.
And so, you know, I'll use that to sponsor an open panel.
I mean, you know, I just want to make sure
I'm able to like continue and like survive
and stuff like that.
Hopefully you guys are having a good night. I'm not mad at anybody. It's like, you know, I
Oh, I don't try to
Whoo for myself
Not trying to like fucking stuff on anybody's toes or anything, you know, I'm just trying to
Have my own do my own thing
You're making jokes about the biscuit. I mean, that's fine. I mean it I don't even care, but it's like that I
Just set that up. So it's like it would just be a troll of me
Something that didn't really bother me as a troll just to see who we'd use it and like some people don't jump all over it
I love limp biscuit. It's one of my favorite bands, you know
So anyway, I finished my coffee I still got another little bit left I just burned myself with a
Brickett thing I can't find my headphones either. I can't find my headphones. I don't know where they are
Kind of frustrating
Because they're kind of big kind of big things to lose right, but I have my own my other ones in the
my
Hopefully I didn't throw them in the laundry. We're doing laundry today guys
Hey, Rudy. Hey, there's Rudy. Hey guys. Good to see you guys
Thank you, Samantha. I will just keep doing me, you know, it's like my show is doing fine
It's like I guess my success will be my best revenge, right?
My success will be my best revenge
And I am successful
And so, you know, I don't have anything negative to say about anybody though
You know, I hope everybody does well. I want everybody to succeed on this platform
not
trying to
again
Bother anybody or step on any toes
There we go lights on
Ooh
Hi guys, yeah, the norwish just inside here. Here's Rudy. Hi, rude. I say hi Rudy. Here's Rudy
Sweet cat
Good kitty cat
Yeah, so I've been doing some cleaning today. I did like four loads of laundry
Um, vacuums, I'm getting my, I got my bedroom in order a little bit.
Um, just trying to get everything good and stuff, but yeah, I love Vita.
Maybe she's just in a bad mood or something like that.
I don't, I don't need to like hurt her feelings, defend her or anybody really.
I'm just trying to, trying to live my life in my show.
Have fun.
Hopefully everyone's having fun. So that's what it's about. Not about hurting anybody's feelings or anything.
Okay
Grab my, I got a couple drinks tonight and
some cigars. I got these backwoods. Now it's like, you know, I was paying $1.50 for two cigars.
Now I'm paying $2.50 for one. Yeah, that's Mr. Rudy right here. Hey Rudy.
Oops, hold on.
Mr. Root. Hey, Mr. Root boy.
He's a cutie, huh?
My cutie Rootie.
Yeah, I love these cats and they keep me going. So whatever happens with any human beings, I
Got my kitty cats here.
I need to find a rival biscuits on to call it the troll beat it back. I don't know
What is it? It's a Persian biscuit. Look at my like a Persian biscuit
I'll keep bringing it up out of nowhere for no reason like hey, it's just a Persian biscuit song. What what what?
Just I'm just playing a nice song. It's just a Persian biscuit, right?
I'm just kidding. Hey J dog. How are you guys?
So I used to burn myself a little bit. I don't see my my frickin my headphones. That's really weird
Oh, I don't know you're right. It's like like what I
Don't want I don't want to troll though. I like I love I don't like to troll my friends like I
Understand why we have to fight right now
Yeah, but I don't know if there's a Persian biscuit song or what but maybe we'll find it
So these are pretty disgusting cigars
These are like backwards it looks like I was made in the back woods of like look at this look at this crap
So I have a smoke today. I
Will get my I will have to fix my camera, you know, I'm in I'm in this like you know
It's like kind of I have to look down at it right now, but how do I look? I look pretty good
Feeling pretty good tonight. Let's see. Let me put these headphones off
Yeah, it's just like my equilibrium is off a little because my ears clog like it's one ears clog
I'm gonna have to try to like
Get it out in the bath
But it's a little bit clogged. I'm gonna find my headphones. I don't know what happened to those
I hear something clanking around in the washing machine.
I'm getting kind of concerned that I accidentally
put them in the washing machine,
but hopefully that did not happen.
Hi guys, hey J-Dog, hey J-Base,
Cowboy's time, deviless.
Yeah, so just know that whatever good times I was saying,
he doesn't understand my show.
He's not even, I think he's come onto my show a few times
and just like, you know, he insulted me,
which is not really, it's like,
why would I go onto somebody's show
and just start insulting them?
No.
I would polite and say, hey, you're a fellow content creator.
Let's work on something together.
Let's collaborate and let's friendly.
I don't know.
Everyone wants to get mad at me, right?
OK.
So anyway, here I go.
But I can't wait to show you.
I will show you guys.
When I get my laundry done, I'll show you my other rooms
in this house.
It'll be pretty cool.
I just don't see.
My headphones tonight, so, you know, I don't know.
I'm gonna keep looking for them.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
What could I have done with them guys?
What could I have done with my headphones?
I don't know.
They're not in my bedroom.
I'm concerned what I did with them.
Okay.
Well, let's just hope they didn't go in the washing machine. That'd just be the end of it, but
Okay, here I come
Hey, we're how we guys doing
You once have to ear your drumming it was so dizzy. Yeah, that's how mine is kind of feeling right now
it's kind of feeling like
Kind of feeling kind of blocked up a little bit and uncomfortable and
It takes off my equilibrium a little bit
But anyway, I've got a third drink in this ice mash, hopefully these couple of drinks
will hit me good.
I'll take a rival biscuit song to bridge the gap.
I don't know.
I mean, how about a happy, you know, the KFC theme song, what's a finger licking good
or something like that?
I don't know.
What can I do guys?
Can you help me mend fences?
So anyway, we had daddy big miss on yesterday. He is a really cool guy. Hey look at wildcard Wednesday
Save to watch later. I'm gonna put my link up. So you guys
Feel free to come up tonight. No charge, you know, no no sponsor needed because we did have a sponsor
I don't know if they want to be mentioned but they did sponsor and so I'm gonna throw throw in a panel for them because
There's like an awesome person
Also
I want to say Christine was saying she didn't want to come to my chat again
Can you guys let Christine know that I will if she wants someone blocked and I saw who they want blocked
I will block those that person for them, you know because
Where Christine does a lot more appreciated than what the other person has done for me, so like you don't need to prove it yourself
You have a successful channel and business. So what do you keep doing? It's yeah, it's it is it is
But it's like, you know, I've made money this month and then a bit business like with all the slander and everything
It's like is it people gonna want to continue donating if they they hear all this crap about me and
You know, like I'm just like the worst person in the world. I'm doing all these bad things not doing anything bad
I'm just trying to do my show. Thank you time
Yeah, I can do a biscuit song Persian biscuit song. Yeah, I'll do a AI Persian biscuit song about beta and then
We'll see if she likes it
No, I think I think she would I think you would okay. Thank you time. Thank you dog
I want to continue to be, have a, you know, members.
I want to continue to have active panelists.
I want to continue to have people kickoff people at the panel.
I want to continue to sponsor panels.
I like all these ideas.
Some of the ideas are adapted from other shows.
Some are my own.
If it works for me, maybe it will work for you.
You know?
Okay.
Hopefully she'll laugh at it, you know?
I don't want to hurt anybody's feelings, you know, I love uh, and I love Vita
Hope uh, I think we're cool. I am a mod on her channel. So it's like it obviously she's like not that bad. Hey, what's up, rude?
Give me some in some please ease off. Yeah
Rudy's very soft cat though. He's a very soft cat
I do not like these fleas so
How are we guys doing tonight?
It's okay. It's okay. I don't feel it. I don't feel like that attack. I feel like you know misunderstood a little bit
And then whatever I try to defend myself. It's like, you know, there's so many people against me that it's like
I don't feel like it's really a fair fight
But yeah, you don't have to you don't have to apologize for her
Whatever whatever people think about me fine, so
Mmm
Okay, yeah, it seems like every few days we like make up so I think we'll be okay
Whoo, so I have a ham and cheese baguette I've been cleaning up my place a lot so
Then got a couple of drinks
Just hanging out with you guys
Let me see
Breakup or makeup. I know but I don't feel like breaking. I mean, it's like I don't have anything against her
I don't still understand like she gets mad at me
Every few days, it's okay
So
Yeah, and also like about like last night like I came on at like 11 30
I just woke up. I forgot that Spunky was starting her show like at 10 30
So I was already like an hour late
Then I got kind of caught up in a conversation with SD Monstro
and so I just you know sent people over to Spunky's chat and
That's regards from my chat and stuff like that and I'll catch her chat as soon as I can it's just like I already started and
I had only been on for a little bit and I wasn't planning on being up for very much longer. So
Okay, well, hopefully everything's okay. Hopefully everything's okay. Let's just
Give everyone a little break and I'm not mad at her at all
If I'm the easy target, let me just be the easy target.
I'd rather be than somebody else, right?
Okay.
Yeah, so it might be a shorter night tonight.
I'm not feeling 100% this week, you guys know.
Here's a couple of books I got, a couple of books.
So, good to see you guys, thanks for coming in.
We'll hang out for a little bit if you don't want to come on panel and say hi. It's not then
you know
You can always come on later
But hopefully everything's good with you guys
my
What's up big rod? What's up buttercup nut nut nut?
How are you big rod? I don't think I've seen you before welcome to my show
Everybody welcome to make last thoughts I can see
I got a lot of people on TikTok, too.
I've been trying to send over here and say hi.
If you have some TikTok shout out in the chat,
good to see you.
Welcome to the show.
Hopefully, there we go.
Time, I think you got a fan in the chat.
part of me guys that was really that was uncalled for I'm so sorry okay so I
yeah also I made some money today just by cleaning out my under my couch and
you see there's at least 50 cents and a kind of $2 and I can't pocket there we
So guys, I didn't tell you I got accepted to the Amazon
influencer program and I would
Let you know like Amazon does have an influencer program where you can like
make a little videos and stuff about your favorite products and and maybe like the
You know an influencer and showing people what you buy and maybe they'll
You know fluency by it too. And so you can check out
Amazon influencer program and apply for that
I was accepted, so I think if you have a decent amount of people on your channel and subscribers, you can probably be accepted in that, too.
Maybe have another monetization thing. It's better to have a lot of flows of monetization, you know?
The more the better, the easier they are, the better.
I've been also working with ChatGPT a lot. I really recommend you guys talk to ChatGPT about...
Your business or your ideas you can ask it. What are 10?
You know low-cost businesses to start like these businesses you can name some other business
You've done it will give you kind of in the genre of the area that what you're looking for
Maybe easy startups and then we'll walk you through it step by step of how to get it started. It's really amazing
So I recommend taking you out to chat since it's a tea for that
Hi, babe. Hi. Oh
Rudy's happy tonight
So anyway, how's everyone doing shout out to everybody in the chat tonight?
Look up you like my
The colors and stuff pretty cool
That was actually one of my first purchases on team and I was like wow that works pretty good
of course, I can't stop it from changing colors all the time now, but
Pretty cool still
Go through all the different colors
Hopefully it's not too psychedelic for you
epilepsy warning right okay okay I'm gonna write the biscuit song and so here
guys I'll just put this video on just real quick and I'll be right back in
like three minutes I'm gonna write the biscuit song I'll try to produce it
and everything I'll just put it on this video just real quick this will take
three minutes okay I'll be right back
It's 9 p.m. Lights up Mike's hot chaos in the stream Vita calling in slurring words starting up the scene talking all that trash
Then she flips rage queen mad at me girl, please the show runs on caffeine
Scythe twisted laughing loud whiskey in his veins slurs flying left and right we cut the feed no shame
But the chats on fire can't tame this flame. This ain't your mama's podcast. This a runaway train
Welcome to the madness buckle up tight boot flashing on cam chat losing their minds Mike
getting gong. Alex taking flight. It's wild, it's wrong, and we do it every night.
Paige got him simping, heart's in the chat, but she ain't got time for a dude like that.
Diamond flirting hard, let the girls react. It's a freak show party, no filter, all facts. Yo.
Yo Michael drops a line gong not tonight Alex try to joke boom sent into the night panel looking sideways
Someone's got a fight producers on mute praying this don't spike diamonds feeling spicy shirts slipping down low
Oops, she says with a wink. That's the whole show sides half asleep. I still cracking jokes slurred out wisdom with a bourbon so glow
No rules just rolls. We pretend to play
And we're trending in the press welcome to the madness buckle up tight
Hey, back. Hey, guys, guess what? We have the premiere of the Persian biscuit song. It's gonna come out in a couple minutes
The AI is just finishing putting some finishing touches on it. I had it written and almost completed
So you guys are gonna be in for a treat here. We have the Persian biscuit song
It looks like it's just uh, oh here we go. It's almost done
Um, it's gonna be done in an air. Hold on
I think you guys will enjoy it.
Hopefully it'll be funny and, you know,
not offensive or anything.
I just want it to be a good, a good fun.
Hi, Bush Boogie.
Hi, Spunky, how are you?
Okay, is it almost done?
Okay, it's still in the process,
but it is a pretty fast, fast program.
So it should be done in just a few minutes.
Pretty exciting.
This is my sweet revenge, but it's all in good fun, guys.
It's all in good fun.
Oh, I love pizza.
Okay, so, let me just test it one second.
Okay, guys, I'm gonna try, this is a gamble.
This is a gamble, let me try it.
Okay, I'm gonna sit down.
Sleep this one, music, add music, okay, drive, save from Chrome.
Let's see what it's going to do.
Save from Chrome.
Hold on.
I'm trying to keep the chair in the chair.
Come on.
Hold on, guys.
Okay, it says download complete.
Hold on.
Okay, resets.
Come on, shared.
Downloads, come on.
It might be on the wrong drive over there, but let me see.
Five.
All right, I found it.
I found it.
OK, here we go, guys.
Here's the Persian distance.
with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work but baby
those scones are drier than Tehran where's the honey sauce girl it's gone
you say you're the queen of the big off crew but your butter slipped out like it's
dodging you I've got saffron cardamom rosewater drizzle you brought
confusion and a half big
Oh, here. Not over. Oh, shit.
I mean, it's not terrible.
Well, Big Rod, you kind of suck.
Someone, someone, uh, kind of, Big Rod. Big Rod.
Just so negative. I mean it.
Okay, thank you so much, Shady.
There's actually another version. I'm gonna try the other version
It sucked okay type him out please
And maybe that wasn't the best version
Yeah, we're trying this one now. Let's see if this is better. It's another version you might like this better
It's taking a long time to process.
Maybe that's good.
That's pretty good, but you need a little memory.
Yeah, I know.
Well, it gives you a couple of options,
but this one's just taking forever.
Good process.
Oh, here, it's ready.
Okay, let's try this one.
["Persian Funk"]
Persian funk meets penny poetic justice.
Bita came through with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones were drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the bake-off crew, but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron cardamom rose water drizzle you brought confusion and a half baked fizzle. I'm the biscuit of
Under desert lights my biscuits got hips my biscuit
Yeah, I think I like that one better
Do you think we have a winner guys? I didn't know it's a winner. What do you think?
What's up, Evil Rod McDonald
It's only a beat in here you hear the song
Hi guys, I don't know what's wrong with everybody tonight. They're not you guys
All right, be here.
Thank you for timing up, people.
It was pretty good?
I like that better, yeah.
It was pretty good.
To do it in 10 minutes, or less than 10 minutes,
get a pretty good song out of it.
I think I'm doing pretty well.
Yeah, I knew a lot about Persian culture that I didn't know.
And I also said B to Jew, and that's what people call her.
I don't know what that means, but B to Jew.
Hi everybody
Here and people are coming in so the link is pinned
And look it's like two out in here or something. I'm gonna drink a couple couple drinks and maybe go to bed early
I don't know
Seems like it's gonna be another one of those quiet nights
But you know I like the
If people that talk shit about AI, it's like, I think should be the end, because AI in conjunction
with human intelligence, like you put the two together, you don't just let the AI go wild
and just do whatever it wants, you direct it, and it can be awesome.
I don't think people understand that.
Yeah, I give way too many of my secrets, too, but it's like I have a whole band in here
That was pretty good.
Hey, Ruth.
Hi.
So how are we doing tonight?
We have cards or something?
Let me see.
Where's my...
Let me check out what it is.
What is this?
A gesture?
These are good.
Hi, guys.
Give me a good shuffle.
Guys, check out my TikTok, by the way.
I do like, you know, my kind of fast readings on there,
but it actually really works there.
Like people actually just like all want readings there.
And that's pretty much all they want.
They don't want like any bit of bullshit.
And so, you know, it's kind of like different
from this show a little bit than that.
It's like, you know, focus on the readings
and stuff like that.
But, you know, this is my YouTube baby.
I thought we'll see how it goes.
I do get some kind of explanations there, too.
I have a membership there, too, already.
Monetized within three days.
New record, huh, guys?
Just the animal.
Where we got for the chat.
Just collected for the chat.
These are really cool.
Oh, look what popped out.
Okay, so we got the four of pentacles.
Okay, four of pentacles.
I'd say coming together
Maybe two couples or something coming together with an idea that could make a lot of money
I don't know if you're you're in a couple and then you know a couple
The four could be the magic number. Thank you Samantha
Okay, also war is like really like you got a you got a hold on the material world thing, right?
What else we got we got the sun. Oh all positive things the sun is all positive all good things the glorious fairy tale castle
The happily ever after the prince and the princess say that everything's good. Everything's bigger. Okay
That's what everyone is looking for
That's son, right? Okay. What else?
We got the Wheel of Fortune things are going in your favor or the Wheel of Fortune is going in your favor right now
I love the colors here, too beautiful like
green and pink
Yeah, Wheel of Fortune
Things are on your side. If you're on Wheel of Fortune, you'd be hitting the $10,000 $10,000 segment up the bank, right?
Okay, what else do you have the Emperor?
Maybe this is like a mature man. This is this one's kind of like Japanese
Yeah, this looks like a all the kings in the deck basically the Emperor
When he says goes he rules over the entire kingdom not just you know the Empire Empire not just the kingdoms, right?
There's maybe four kingdoms in the Empire
Use the head honcho, right? So I'm gonna charge through the meatless person. You are this person. What else?
Three of swords
Watch out. There's some heartbreak ahead. Maybe two, you know, you want to watch out
Don't get your hopes up too high certain situations and go with the flow and you will heal from any heartbreak, too
But that's not the best news. Let's get some advice for the chat
Two of swords is like maybe like, you know get out of like the tunnel vision
You're coming to a crossroads make the right choice cut what doesn't serve out of your life to your sword
They always think of it as a pair of scissors
Cut what doesn't serve you also like a television set though because
Like they're doing like this, right? Just taking the TV set. So thank you, Samantha. Well, that was the collective for the chat
You want to come on the panel? I don't know maybe
It's looking a little bit quiet these days I
Don't know. Why do I get so tired though? I get these I get these like shutters of
I think it's because I've been smoking this fake
The bait makes me sleepy, but I do have a couple beers. I'm gonna try to use a couple beers and
Hang out as long as I can
Wonder when beat is gonna get here
I read, yeah, I'm reading the energies of the chat, yeah.
And it does tire me out sometimes.
Sometimes it gives me energy,
sometimes it takes a little bit of energy, you know,
it does both, you know.
So maybe I'm a little bit extra sensitive to these.
I don't know, how's the moon right now?
We are in the Leo season,
so it does kind of burb right during the day.
Yeah.
I also had this protection soap I use and the soap really like, you know, it makes a difference, I think that's a really good soap, it's called Oliwe or something, Oliwe, Oliwe.
Smells really good.
So yeah, so my hair is getting pretty out of control, huh?
So I'm going to sit back with Rudy right here.
There's Rudy.
Hi guys.
We're more sage, yeah, I will in a little bit.
I'm almost out of my face too.
Do I look like, maybe I look like really dorky
and some people think I'm like really dorky,
but I'm really not.
It's like, I like, I like how glasses can like
change the perception of a person sometimes.
Hopefully it's not like all Jeffrey Dahmer thoughts, right?
But I like these a lot.
I like these glasses.
If you want to come up on the panel, I think I did pin the link.
By the way, they were talking about the paywall I do have.
I do have a paywall up because I get threatened so much with like, you know, flagging my videos
that I've just put behind the paywall.
After I do the show, the lives are all free, but after I do the show, I put them on members
I show nice and protected from the haters and stuff like that so
Members and there's a lot of members of over a hundred so they can see all the past episodes
Except the ones that are private and I have to go through those myself because some of those were probably form bombs
There's different stuff and so I'm gonna make sure I don't get any any trouble on YouTube. So
But how are we guys we're doing guys? I hope we're having a great day today. It was the 30th
So you have a few more days of a month
You want to have any questions or comments or
Ideas or all of our things I need to go over there because you that has had a few drinks
Okay, I will but say I want to play her the song and I can't play the song over there. I can just play it over here
There's a lot of weirds like you, but I love you Ilya and Ilya's porn bomb me, but it's like
We're cool though because there's a chance he had once time he had a chance to form on me
He did it. I fell asleep with him on the panel
And I don't know if it was divine intervention or something. Hey, what's up? Oh, Lola. Hey, Lola. Hey, Juan Lola
Okay over here. Hi
Hi Lola
Yeah, oh you're hissing at Rudy
Hi everybody, there's you right there. We're coming to you up. Yeah, so I don't see my headphones around. Yeah, let's miss Lola
Lola Lola likes to
Stay in the house a lot. Hi, babe
Yeah, Nora came in. Hey, there's tricks to your tricks is up there my tricks
Yeah, Lenore knows Lenore is just in you just root me. You don't do form bounds
Well remember when you took a pee in that in that yellow bucket and we saw your wiener
You want to pick purchase a show of Jamie's Cowboys at the farmers market. Yeah
Jamie get yourself on Amazon and stuff and then I'll I can promote it on my I'm not an Amazon
influencer
So I can promote products on Amazon. Oh
You don't sell stage Jamie. Jamie sells honey. I think she sells honey. Do you sell honey products too?
But Jamie's like a beekeeper
But maybe you should grow some sage because sage is a you know, wonderful wonderful crop
I think you probably can probably can make some dough from it too
The cats yeah make some honey
It'd be so cool to learn about honey and like to be in a little beaker outfit with like the smoker thing and like
Like watch the queen bee and like, I don't know
Drives like a slimy burger
You know hug him and Rudy. Yes, I give you a hug
Hi, it's from Jamie's cowboys
How are you?
Yep, you guys having fun come up on panel say hi to me
They got the panel open tonight. It's free panel open panel. We did have a beautiful sponsor earlier that
Timed out Canada Drive for the next 24 hours. And so hey rude. Oh, here comes Rudy
Hi, we're all coming up here. Say hi
You listen go hit them. Hi
You all get attention here they all come
Hi guys
Also my tiktok guys join my tiktok. It's fun. It's like quick readings, but wow, it's fun over there
There I think the taste though tiktok
And shit. Yeah, there we go. Let me just click on that link
I don't know if I get
Counts for inviting you guys
What's to sponsor tonight's panel?
It was an anonymous donor that timed out Canada dry and so if they want me to say their name
I will but I'm just sponsoring the panel in honor of them, but they're not anonymous as far as I know right now
Let's take step forward
It's a secret person
Timing out Canada dry
You have only YouTube and rumble. I don't know but tiktok is cool. I don't know. I think people like this
See, there's a really sexy people on tiktok. I would say they're
Or sexy and they're
Guys that likes it. Oh my god. It's fun. I
love Canada Drive ginger ale but
And I like the person Canada Drive but somebody has timed him out past three days in a
Persian funk meets penny poetic justice
Bita came through with a tray and a smirk
Talking about biscuits like she did the work, but baby those scones were drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the bake-off crew but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you
I brought saffron, cardamom, rose, water, drizzle
You brought confusion and a half-baked fizzle
I'm the biscuit of Babylon lake
Okay, do you hear me now?
Can you hear me now? Not there's problems. I'd have to go on my other by this thing actually
Can you hear me?
Audio hello, do you hear me now? Oh, yeah, I think you do
Okay, good ten four
Okay, do we hear the song here you go if I can hear it
You tease with a tune about your beat to bite
But I serve mine warm under desert lights
My biscuits got hips, my biscuits got pride
Yours needs butter just to slide
I got Fok Levoi cousins and Toddy Groot
Your recipes lost in the back of my boots
Whip that dough like you're in a trance
But you'll never beat a Persian dance
Beat to June, this is not a biscuit
This is construction material
I think it booted off. Hold on. Let's see. Hold on one second. We have base stirfer. Hold on. Let's take it. I've heard of you. Hold on one second.
It's the same person. Let me just put my banner up. Hold on. Hello. Nager, Nager, Nager.
Well, I mean, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a, what a
Justice
Bita came through with a tray and a smirk talking about biscuits like she did the work
But baby those scones were drier than Tehran. Where's the honey sauce girl? It's gone
You say you're the queen of the bake-off crew, but your butter slipped out like it's dodging you I brought saffron
Cardamom rose water drizzle you brought confusion and a half baked fizzle. I'm the best
under desert lights my biscuit's got hips my biscuit's got pride yours needs butter just a slide
i got baklava cousins and toddy roots your recipes a lot
oh hey what's up you like this song oh good yeah it was pretty good it's a new biscuit song i mean
it's like i think i think it's better than the other one i prefer baklava over the biscuit yeah
How are you God pretty good man? What's going on? Oh
Not too much. I found my headphones finally. I love these ones pooped out on me. So I'm just having a smash and
Hanging out. It was a little bit rough at beat us today. So what happened? Oh
You know, she had good times good times. Oh
So he doesn't allow anyone on the panel list. They pay their members and like it's like just untrue things and then she was like
Oh, thank you. Oh, I you know, I I said the white biscuit and then you go mad. Why?
It's like it's just like my you know, I couldn't take it anymore. I just
were just being mean to me on the panel and
So I just left but I don't think you mind one person being mean to you. It's when you get gangbanged up there
Yeah, and I was like five
Elda was nice to me, you know, I mean if it was gangbanging if they mean just use some Lou but at least I mean come on
They're so so rough. I mean, but uh, you know elder was up there. He was nice and like clumsy
He was fine, but it's like, you know good times hates me and you know, Canada's not a fan. Yeah, I know
There is misrepresenting my show and like and then like you know saying oh
The money he's scamming people. He's like he's not gonna tear up blah blah blah blah and it's just like why why are you so negative about me?
It's like everything everyone wants to judge me about everything and I'm actually like out here
Doing it making some money on YouTube and like you know and I'm not
Do it your way if it doesn't work